LEONARD:
Oh, great.
-Your mom is not coming, right?
-Not this time. I promise.
(Raj:)Just to be clear,
roller-skating was my idea.
I'm unhappy
that you turned it into a date...
(Raj:)...and I hope you both fall on your asses
and break your coccyxes.
The plural of "coccyx" is "coccyges."
(Raj:)Screw you.
Give me back my lima beans.
(Bernadette:)Oh, my God.
Have you ever been so embarrassed?
(Penny:)Not recently.
(Bernadette:)I don't know which was lamer,
their roller skating or their disco dancing.
(Penny:)For me, the worst part was when
people saw us leave with them.
(Leonard:)You had some nice moves out there,
Howard.
(Howard:)-Thanks. You too.
-You noticed all the people looking at us?
(Howard:)Not really. I was in my boogie zone.
-And when Howard tried to do the splits?
-Shh.
Sorry, I'm moving slow.
(Leonard:)-I think I bruised my coccyx.
-Aw, poor baby.